jizz.best 2015-12-20

# jizz.best - you deserve the best porn

**Effective Date:** January 24, 2015

**Last Modified:** January 24, 2015

#### I. General

The operative parties referred to in this policy are Company and You, the User of this site. jizz.best is the publisher and operator of this site.  
Hereinafter, jizz.best shall be referred to as "Company". When first-person pronouns are used in this policy, (Us, We, Our, Ours, etc.) these provisions  
are referring to Company. Additionally, when the terms "the Site" or "Site" are used, these terms refer to the website(s) listed at the beginning of this policy.

You, the User – as the User of this Site, this policy will refer to the User as "You" or through any applicable second-person pronouns, such as "Yours", etc.  
Hereinafter, the User of the Site shall be referred to in applicable second-person pronouns. This policy describes how we use information received about You  
when You visit Our Site or when You subscribe to, or otherwise use Our online services. This policy does not cover any information that We may receive  
from or about You through channels other than through the use of the Site. 

#### II. Revisions to this Policy

We reserve the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy and Our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner.  
You should periodically check for any modifications of this policy by re-visiting this web page and using the "refresh" button on Your browser.  
You should note the date of last revision to this policy, which appears at the top of this policy. If the "last modified" date remains unchanged after  
You have clicked the "refresh" button on Your browser, You may presume that no changes have been made since the last reading of the policy.  
A changed "last modified" dates indicates that this policy has been updated or edited, and the new version supersedes any prior versions immediately upon posting. 

#### III. Personal Information that We Collect

Given the nature of Our Site, Users are limited to a single-level of interactivity with the Site and as such, are labeled as Browsers.  
We do not provide memberships of any kind. Any registration, memberships or subscriptions made available via the Site are provided in part or entirely  
by third parties regardless of any branding or names associated with such memberships. The Site is not responsible for the activities of any third party  
or the content of any third party site, including a third party's passive or active collection of Your information and any such party's subsequent use of Your information.

Browsers are visitors to the Site who never enter into any active data collection pages.  
This information is restricted to cookies, IP Addresses and Referral URLs, and other passive information gathering devices (explained below). 

#### IV. How We Collect Information from You

  * **Passive Collection**  
We use cookies to collect information about You in order to enhance Your experience on the Site.  
The information collected in Our cookies includes, but is not limited to, Your User IP address, geographic location and other session data. 
  * **Active Collection**  
We do not engage in active data collection of any kind. Should you reach a feature requesting personal information from You (e.g. registration process  
and/or membership form), You understand and agree that such information is requested by a third party, regardless of any branding or names associated  
with such a party or website. The Site is not responsible for data collection of Your information and any such party's subsequent use of Your information. 

#### V. How We Use Your Information

The primary use for Your information is to provide You with services You have requested. We also use Your information to deliver customized services to You.  
Non-personal and aggregate information, such as that collected passively is used in order to customize Our marketing efforts or to customize the use of Our Site  
for an aggregate group of customers. We also use Your information for market research purposes – in order to increase Your (and other Users') experience according  
to tracked interests, to analyze and target potential new markets, and for other marketing purposes. 

#### VI. Special Cases

It is Our policy not to use or share the personal information about Browsers in ways unrelated to those described in this policy without also providing You  
an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. However, We may disclose personal information, or information regarding Your use  
of the services or Site(s) accessible through Our services, for any reason if, in Our sole discretion, We believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: 

  * To satisfy any laws, such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, regulations, or governmental, or legal requests for such information
  * To disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Terms & Conditions or other policies
  * To operate Our services properly
  * To protect ourselves, Our Browsers, and the general public

We specifically reserve the right to disclose any and all information to law enforcement in the event that a crime is committed, is suspected, or if We are compelled  
to do so by lawful criminal, civil, or administrative process, discovery requests, subpoenas, court orders, writs, or reasonable request of authorities or persons with  
the reasonable power to obtain such process. We will always cooperate with law enforcement authorities, government agencies, and private-party litigants seeking  
information about Our users to the extent required by applicable law, or if we are legally advised to do so.

Examples of such cooperation include but are not limited to, lawful criminal, civil, or administrative process, discovery requests, subpoenas, court orders, writs  
or reasonable request of authorities or persons with the reasonable power to obtain such process. 

#### VII. Public Forums & Other Public Areas

If at any time during Your visit to the Site, You enter into a public forum or interactive communication feature such as, registration requests, chat sessions  
or discussion boards, You have exited Our Site. We do not provide such features on Our Site, therefore, You understand and agree  
that the Site is not responsible for any content shared or distributed via such interactive features. 

#### VIII. Our Commitment to Data Security

We take measures to protect the transmission of all sensitive user information. We make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of Our network and systems.  
Nevertheless, We cannot guarantee that Our security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information.

We take all reasonable measures to prevent such breaches of security, but given the resourcefulness of cyber-criminals, We are unable to guarantee that Our security  
is one hundred percent (100%) breach-proof. You assume the risk of such breaches to the extent that they occur despite Our reasonable security measures. 

#### IX. Where to Direct Questions About Our Privacy Policy

If You have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, You may contact Us.
